<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <UnskilledLaborSpeed.label>unskilled labor speed</UnskilledLaborSpeed.label>
    <UnskilledLaborSpeed.description>The speed at which this person carries out unskilled labor like making stone blocks, making chemfuel at a refinery or burning items.</UnskilledLaborSpeed.description>

	<SculptingSpeed.label>彫刻・速度</SculptingSpeed.label>
	<SculptingSpeed.description>The speed at which this person creates sculptures.\n\nThis stat only affects the how fast sculptures are produced, not their quality. Quality is determined by the sculptor's artistic skill.</SculptingSpeed.description>

    <TailoringSpeed.label>縫製・速度</TailoringSpeed.label>
    <TailoringSpeed.description>The speed at which this person makes clothes.\n\nThis stat only affects how fast clothes are produced, not their quality. Quality is determined by the tailor's crafting skill.</TailoringSpeed.description>

	<SmithingSpeed.label>鍛冶・速度</SmithingSpeed.label>
	<SmithingSpeed.description>Speed at which this person crafts weapons, machinery, and ammunition.\n\nThis stat only affects how fast items are produced, not their quality. Quality is determined by the crafter's skill.</SmithingSpeed.description>

    <DrugSynthesisSpeed.label>薬物生成・速度</DrugSynthesisSpeed.label>
    <DrugSynthesisSpeed.description>薬物を調合して生成する速度です。</DrugSynthesisSpeed.description>
<!--
    <StonecuttingSpeed.label>石材加工・速度</StonecuttingSpeed.label>
    <StonecuttingSpeed.description>ストーンカットする速度です。</StonecuttingSpeed.description>
-->

    <CookSpeed.label>調理・速度</CookSpeed.label>
    <CookSpeed.description>食事を作る速度です。</CookSpeed.description>

	<FoodPoisonChance.label>食中毒・発生率</FoodPoisonChance.label>
	<FoodPoisonChance.description>The probability that this character will inadvertently poison a meal they cook. Food poison temporarily debilitates anyone it strikes.</FoodPoisonChance.description>

	<DrugCookingSpeed.label>drug cooking speed</DrugCookingSpeed.label>
	<DrugCookingSpeed.description>The speed at which this person brews beer and tea, or makes simple drug products like smokeleaf joints.</DrugCookingSpeed.description>

    <ButcheryFleshSpeed.label>食肉加工・速度</ButcheryFleshSpeed.label>
    <ButcheryFleshSpeed.description>食肉加工する速度です。</ButcheryFleshSpeed.description>

    <ButcheryFleshEfficiency.label>食肉加工・収率</ButcheryFleshEfficiency.label>
    <ButcheryFleshEfficiency.description>The amount of meat produced when butchering flesh creatures. The actual amount is also related to the creature's size.</ButcheryFleshEfficiency.description>

    <ButcheryMechanoidSpeed.label>メカノイド・解体速度</ButcheryMechanoidSpeed.label>
    <ButcheryMechanoidSpeed.description>メカノイドを解体する速度です。</ButcheryMechanoidSpeed.description>

    <ButcheryMechanoidEfficiency.label>メカノイド・解体収率</ButcheryMechanoidEfficiency.label>
    <ButcheryMechanoidEfficiency.description>The amount of materials yielded when this person disassembles a dead mechanoid. The actual amount is also related to the mechanoid's size.</ButcheryMechanoidEfficiency.description>

    <SmeltingSpeed.label>精錬・速度</SmeltingSpeed.label>
    <SmeltingSpeed.description>The speed at which this person smelts things.\n\nSince smelting is dumb labor, smelting speed is not affected by any skill.</SmeltingSpeed.description>

</LanguageData>