<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<!--=============== AI persona core ====================-->

	<AIPersonaCore.label>AI人格コア</AIPersonaCore.label>
	<AIPersonaCore.description>天才と同等な高度な人工知能を納めた、非常に進んだコンピュータコア。本体より分離されて休止状態にありますが、しかるべき所へインストールされれば驚くべき力を発揮します。</AIPersonaCore.description>

	<!--=============== Neurotrainer ====================-->

	<MechSerumNeurotrainer.label>ニューロトレイナーシーラム</MechSerumNeurotrainer.label>
	<MechSerumNeurotrainer.description>A one-use super-dose of mechanites tuned to train a specific skill. The dose is administered through the orbit of the eye. Once released into the brain, the mechanites quickly improve the subject's skills in a specific area, transmuting themselves into neural tissue as needed.</MechSerumNeurotrainer.description>
    <MechSerumNeurotrainer.comps.1.useLabel>{0}を学ぶためにニューロトレイナーシーラムを使う</MechSerumNeurotrainer.comps.1.useLabel>

    <MechSerumHealer.label>ヒーラーシーラム</MechSerumHealer.label>
    <MechSerumHealer.description>使い捨て大容量ナノマシーンを健康状態を回復させる機能に特化させてあります。ナノマシーンは、患者の最も悪い一カ所の部位を回復させます。普通の方法では治すことができないケガや症状でさえも、健康な状態に戻します。ナノマシーンは有機質の中で変形すらでき、必要であれば新しい手足や内臓に形を変えることができます。</MechSerumHealer.description>
    <MechSerumHealer.comps.1.useLabel>ヒーラーシーラムを使う</MechSerumHealer.comps.1.useLabel>

    <MechSerumResurrector.label>リザレクトシーラム</MechSerumResurrector.label>
    <MechSerumResurrector.description>A one-use super-dose of mechanites tuned to resurrect the dead. Administered to a corpse soon after death, mechanites repair broken-down tissues and kickstart the body back to life. Unfortunately, the resurrected sometimes come back with brain damage, blindness, or progressive psychosis. Outcomes are better when the mechanites are administered to a fresher body. Well-preserved bodies can be resurrected, even long after death.</MechSerumResurrector.description>
    <MechSerumResurrector.comps.1.useLabel>リザレクトシーラムを使う</MechSerumResurrector.comps.1.useLabel>

	<TechprofSubpersonaCore.label>研究AI亜人格コア</TechprofSubpersonaCore.label>
	<TechprofSubpersonaCore.description>簡素な人工知能を収めた、この小型のAIコアは教育用テクノロジーに特化しています。使用すると、AIは貴方の未収得なテクノロジー一つを即座に習得させます、一度限りしか使用できません。</TechprofSubpersonaCore.description>
	<TechprofSubpersonaCore.comps.1.useLabel>研究AI亜人格コアを使う</TechprofSubpersonaCore.comps.1.useLabel>
	<!--=============== Thrumbo horn ====================-->

	<ThrumboHorn.label>スランボの角</ThrumboHorn.label>
	<ThrumboHorn.description>A thrumbo's horn. It's razor-sharp, rock-hard, and priceless in most markets. This is a true trophy, as well as a deadly melee weapon.</ThrumboHorn.description>
    <ThrumboHorn.tools.0.label>突起</ThrumboHorn.tools.0.label>
    <ThrumboHorn.tools.1.label>基部</ThrumboHorn.tools.1.label>

	<!--=============== Elephant tusk ====================-->

	<ElephantTusk.label>象の牙</ElephantTusk.label>
	<ElephantTusk.description>An elephant's tusk. It is very durable and valuable. While somewhat unwieldy as a melee weapon, it can still be deadly.</ElephantTusk.description>
    <ElephantTusk.tools.0.label>突起</ElephantTusk.tools.0.label>
    <ElephantTusk.tools.1.label>基部</ElephantTusk.tools.1.label>

</LanguageData>
