<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <Elephant.label>ゾウ</Elephant.label>
    <Elephant.description>The largest unmodified land animal. Elephants has a long trunk they use to manipulate objects, and sharp tusks they use to gore attackers. A dead elephant's valuable tusks can be recovered by butchering it.\n\nIntelligent creatures with complex social relationships, elephants can be used as pack animals or trained to carry out the most complex of tasks. They live a long time, and are known to remember events and relationships from many decades before.</Elephant.description>
    <Meat_Elephant.label>ゾウの肉</Meat_Elephant.label>
    <Meat_Elephant.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Elephant.description>
    <Corpse_Elephant.label>ゾウの死骸</Corpse_Elephant.label>
    <Corpse_Elephant.description>ゾウの死骸</Corpse_Elephant.description>

	<Megasloth.label>メガスロス</Megasloth.label>
	<Megasloth.description>A giant, solitary herbivore with two giant claws for warding off threats. Long extinct after being wiped out by the natives of Earth's American continent, the megasloth was later brought back using advanced cloning and artificial gestators. Its thick hide is exceptionally strong and insulating, and makes a great leather for cold-weather clothing.</Megasloth.description>
	<Meat_Megasloth.label>メガスロスの肉</Meat_Megasloth.label>
	<Meat_Megasloth.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Megasloth.description>
	<Corpse_Megasloth.label>メガスロスの死骸</Corpse_Megasloth.label>
	<Corpse_Megasloth.description>メガスロスの死骸</Corpse_Megasloth.description>

    <Thrumbo.label>スランボ</Thrumbo.label>
    <Thrumbo.description>A gigantic, graceful creature of unknown origin. The thrumbo is gentle by nature, but extremely dangerous when enraged. While its long fur is exceptionally beautiful, its hide is also incredibly resistant to damage. Its razor-sharp horn fetches a huge price.\n\nLegends say that an old thrumbo is the wisest creature in the universe - it simply chooses not to speak.</Thrumbo.description>
    <Meat_Thrumbo.label>スランボの肉</Meat_Thrumbo.label>
    <Meat_Thrumbo.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Thrumbo.description>
    <Corpse_Thrumbo.label>スランボの死骸</Corpse_Thrumbo.label>
    <Corpse_Thrumbo.description>スランボの死骸</Corpse_Thrumbo.description>

</LanguageData>