<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

	<Muffalo.label>マッファロー</Muffalo.label>
	<Muffalo.description>A large herding herbivore descended from buffalo and adapted for both cold and warm environments. While enraged muffalo are deadly, tamed muffalo are quite docile and can be used as pack animals.\n\nNobody is quite sure why they're blue - it might even be some early genetic modification test that just never got changed.</Muffalo.description>
	<Meat_Muffalo.label>マッファローの肉</Meat_Muffalo.label>
	<Meat_Muffalo.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Muffalo.description>
	<Corpse_Muffalo.label>マッファローの死骸</Corpse_Muffalo.label>
	<Corpse_Muffalo.description>マッファローの死骸</Corpse_Muffalo.description>

	<Gazelle.label>ガゼル</Gazelle.label>
	<Gazelle.description>小さくて、非常にすばしっこいアンテロープは、信じられないくらいのロングジャンプをすることで有名です。</Gazelle.description>
	<Meat_Gazelle.label>ガゼルの肉</Meat_Gazelle.label>
	<Meat_Gazelle.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Gazelle.description>
	<Corpse_Gazelle.label>ガゼルの死骸</Corpse_Gazelle.label>
	<Corpse_Gazelle.description>ガゼルの死骸</Corpse_Gazelle.description>

	<Iguana.label>イグアナ</Iguana.label>
	<Iguana.description>この大きなトカゲは普段植物を食べています。しかし一旦起こらせると、強い尾っぽと、鋭利な爪は、非常に危険なものとなります。\n\nResting iguanas hold their heads high, giving them an amusing 'proud' look. But they're not proud; they're just trying to see predators so they don't get eaten.</Iguana.description>
	<Meat_Iguana.label>イグアナの肉</Meat_Iguana.label>
	<Meat_Iguana.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Iguana.description>
	<Corpse_Iguana.label>イグアナの死骸</Corpse_Iguana.label>
	<Corpse_Iguana.description>イグアナの死骸</Corpse_Iguana.description>

	<Rhinoceros.label>サイ</Rhinoceros.label>
	<Rhinoceros.description>Despite being herbivorous, this large mammal is very easy to enrage. Once angered, its massive strength and sharp horn make it a brutal opponent. It has more muscle in one leg than most humans do in their whole body.</Rhinoceros.description>
	<Meat_Rhinoceros.label>サイの肉</Meat_Rhinoceros.label>
	<Meat_Rhinoceros.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Rhinoceros.description>
	<Corpse_Rhinoceros.label>サイの死骸</Corpse_Rhinoceros.label>
	<Corpse_Rhinoceros.description>サイの死骸</Corpse_Rhinoceros.description>

	<Dromedary.label>ヒトコブラクダ</Dromedary.label>
	<Dromedary.description>A large land mammal adapted to arid environments. Domesticated since ancient times, its wool and leather are both exceptionally good at insulating against the desert heat, and its milk is quite nourishing. It can be used as a pack animal, but it's bouncing gait makes it too uncomfortable to ride for any distance.\n\nBy storing water in its large humps and reclaiming moisture from its breath as it exhales, it can go weeks without drinking.</Dromedary.description>
	<Meat_Dromedary.label>ヒトコブラクダの肉</Meat_Dromedary.label>
	<Meat_Dromedary.description>生の切り分けられた食用肉。生のままでも、調理して料理にしても、食べることができます。</Meat_Dromedary.description>
	<Corpse_Dromedary.label>ヒトコブラクダの死骸</Corpse_Dromedary.label>
	<Corpse_Dromedary.description>ヒトコブラクダの死骸</Corpse_Dromedary.description>

</LanguageData>