<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <MicroelectronicsBasics.label>マイクロエレクトロニクス 基礎</MicroelectronicsBasics.label>
    <MicroelectronicsBasics.description>微細で複雑な電子工学の基礎です。これによって、ハイテクリサーチベンチ、通信機器、そして、ブラウン管テレビや疑似冷凍睡眠機など、他の研究プロジェクトをアンロックします。</MicroelectronicsBasics.description>

    <TubeTelevision.label>ブラウン管テレビ</TubeTelevision.label>
    <TubeTelevision.description>ブラウン管テレビを作ることが可能になります。</TubeTelevision.description>

    <FlatscreenTelevision.label>flatscreen television</FlatscreenTelevision.label>
    <FlatscreenTelevision.description>Produce high-resolution flatscreen televisions for greater enjoyment.</FlatscreenTelevision.description>

	<Firefoam.label>泡消火器</Firefoam.label>
	<Firefoam.description>Construct firefoam poppers, automatic fire-safety devices which spread fire-retardant foam in response to encroaching flames.</Firefoam.description>

	<MoisturePump.label>土壌改良ポンプ</MoisturePump.label>
	<MoisturePump.description>Construct moisture pumps, which very slowly normalize the moisture in the ground around them. They can turn wet ground dry and convert soft sand into normal sand.</MoisturePump.description>

	<SterileMaterials.label>sterile materials</SterileMaterials.label>
	<SterileMaterials.description>Construct sterile tiles to make cleanrooms for more effective medical treatment and research.</SterileMaterials.description>

	<HospitalBed.label>病院用ベッド</HospitalBed.label>
	<HospitalBed.description>Construct hospital beds which improve medical outcomes.</HospitalBed.description>

    <TransportPod.label>輸送ポッド</TransportPod.label>
    <TransportPod.description>Construct launchable transport pods that you can use to send people and supplies long distances across the planet's surface. Can be used for raiding, travel, sending gifts, and more.</TransportPod.description>

	<MedicineProduction.label>製薬</MedicineProduction.label>
	<MedicineProduction.description>Produce standard industrial-tech medicine by combining herbal medicine, neutroamine, and cloth.</MedicineProduction.description>

	<LongRangeMineralScanner.label>長距離鉱物探査スキャナー</LongRangeMineralScanner.label>
	<LongRangeMineralScanner.description>Construct long-range mineral scanners to detect precious minerals like gold or jade in across the planet. Requires advanced components to construct.</LongRangeMineralScanner.description>

	<ShieldBelt.label>シールドベルト</ShieldBelt.label>
	<ShieldBelt.description>モーメンタム-リパルジョンフィールド技術が、内から外からの遠距離射撃をブロックする、シールドベルトの製造を可能にします。</ShieldBelt.description>

</LanguageData>
